comicbookroundup.com 2019-05-31

# Privacy Policy - Comic Book Reviews

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which Comic Book RoundUp collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a "User") of the http://comicbookroundup.com website ("Site").

## Personal identification information

We may collect personal identification information from Users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when Users visit our site, register on the site, and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site. Users may be asked for, as appropriate, name, email address. Users may, however, visit our Site anonymously. We will collect personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personally identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site related activities.

## Non-personal identification information

We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about Users means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information.

## Subscribe to newsletters and promotional emails

When you receive newsletters or promotional emails from Comic Book RoundUp, we may use cookies and web beacons (described below), customized links or other technologies to recognize you, to determine whether the email has been opened, which links you click. The data is used to help us determine the effectiveness of our communications with you, gather demographic information about our user base, provide you with communications and product and service offerings more tailored to your personal interests, to serve targeted advertising on other websites around the Internet and to provide security.

## Information Collected through Cookies and Similar Tracking Technology

Comic Book RoundUp and our business partners' websites use "cookies" and similar tracking technologies (such as web beacons, tags, scripts and device identifiers). We may receive reports from business partners based on use of these technologies. These reports may provide this information on an individual as well as on an aggregated basis.

## 1\. Cookies

A cookie is a text file that is either stored in your computer's memory temporarily and automatically deleted when you close your browser (a session cookie) or placed on your hard drive (a persistent cookie) by a web page server. A persistent cookie is not deleted when the browser is closed. Comic Book RoundUp uses both session cookies and persistent cookies. Comic Book RoundUp cookies do not save any personal information. You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. Please refer to your web browser for more information. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to sign in or use other interactive features of Comic Book RoundUp websites and services that depend on cookies.

## 2\. Web Beacons

A "web beacon" is an electronic image that can be used to recognize a cookie on your computer when you view a web page or email. Our business partners use web beacons on our websites, in our emails, in our advertisements on other websites (including social media), and in our advertisements contained in third party emails sent to you. Web beacons help us measure the effectiveness of our websites and our advertising in various ways for example, by counting the number of individuals who visit our websites from a particular advertisement or who make a purchase from our websites after viewing a particular advertisement as well as by telling us when a web page is viewed and providing a description of the page where the web beacon is placed. Web beacons also help us measure the effectiveness of our email campaigns, for example, by counting the number of individuals who open or act upon an email message, determining when an email message is opened and determining how many times an email message is forwarded. This helps us send more relevant advertisements to our users and on the websites most visited by you. Unlike cookies, you cannot decline web beacons. However, setting your browser to decline cookies may help prevent web beacons tracking your activity.

## 3\. Analytic Tools

We may use tools such as Google Analytics to better understand who is using our websites and how they are using them. These tools may use cookies and web beacons to save and collect information such as time of visit, pages visited, time spent on each page of the website, IP address, and type of operating system used. We may use this information to manage and improve our websites and to improve your experience with our websites. You can learn how to opt-out of Google Analytics tracking software at this website: <http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout>.

## How we use collected information

Comic Book RoundUp may collect and use Users personal information for the following purposes:

To run and operate our Site - We may need your information display content on the Site correctly. 

To personalize user experience - We may use information in the aggregate to understand how our Users as a group use the services and resources provided on our Site. 

To improve our Site - We may use feedback you provide to improve our products and services. 

To send periodic emails - We may use the email address to send User information and updates pertaining to their account. It may also be used to respond to their inquiries, questions, and/or other requests. Users can opt-out of all emails. 

## How we protect your information

We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, account information and data stored on our Site.

## Sharing your personal information

We do not sell, trade, or rent Users personal identification information to others. We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above. 

## Third party websites

Users may find advertising or other content on our Site that link to the sites and services of our partners, suppliers, advertisers, sponsors, licensors and other third parties. We do not control the content or links that appear on these sites and are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our Site. In addition, these sites or services, including their content and links, may be constantly changing. These sites and services may have their own privacy policies and customer service policies. Browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites which have a link to our Site, is subject to that website's own terms and policies. The information practices of those third-party websites linked to or from our Site are not covered by this Privacy Policy.

## Advertising

Ads appearing on our site may be delivered to Users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile non personal identification information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This privacy policy does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers. You may learn more about opting out of major ad networks at <https://websitebuilders.com/tools/advertiser-opt-out/>.

## Google Adsense

Some of the ads may be served by Google. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to Users based on their visit to our Site and other sites on the Internet. DART uses "non personally identifiable information" and does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, etc. You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at <http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html>

## Compliance with children's online privacy protection act

Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our Site from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 13.

## Changes to this privacy policy

Comic Book RoundUp has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will post a notification on the main page of our Site. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.

## Your acceptance of these terms

By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.

## Contacting us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact us.

This document was last updated on June 1, 2018
